We have another great show for you
tonight here on Command Center. The
prospect professor is back in the
building to talk about the final puzzle
piece in the evaluation process. Our
guys break down the importance of
prodays. Then former NFL quarterback and
third overall pick Shawn Springs joins
the show to share his thoughts of who we
think could fit in Washington. And the
command center crew is gearing up for
another trip to the golf course. And
Fred might still have some work to do.
>> Yes.
Hey,
>> we'll see if smooths improve. All that
and more starts right now.
Welcome in to another episode of Command
Center from here in the Big Bear AI
Command Center studio here with Santana
Moss. Fred Smoo LP Logan Paulson is back
in the building. I'm your host Brian
Cobra Jr. Logan, it's crazy to think
just under two weeks away from the
draft. We just keep getting closer and
closer.
>> Pro days were the part that we just
passed. And during this evaluation
process, we're just two weeks left. Does
much change when you're watching these
prospects? Can prospects do much for
themselves at this point?
>> I don't think a lot changes. I think
obviously the tape is the number one
driver and Fred can attest to that.
That's the thing that really informs the
majority of the draft content. But if
you're trying to finalize the draft
board, those last couple picks sometimes
a good 40 at a proday or catching the
football, running good routes, like
that's the thing that'll differentiate,
you know, player X from player Y and
that'll get somebody drafted as opposed
to not.
>> Well, it's one of them things where
>> you want to leave a good taste in people
mouth and the last time that they see
you is what what's going to make them
remember you or remember your
performance. Like Logan said, the tape
going to speak for itself. Now, what's
going to separate you is do you what's
your athletic prowess? Do you have
something that jumps off the screen? Are
you uh stronger than the average? Are
you faster than the average? What's
going to make me want to pick you? Cuz
you only need one team to like you, not
all 32. You need one team to like you.
>> Yeah. I think those pro days could be
good for guys who are not, you know,
comfortable at performing in front of
which is kind of odd if you're a
football player, but you know, sometime
people don't test well. Some people
shot.
>> Yeah. Some days the guys say, "All
right, I can get back to my own domain
and where I'm where I'm comfortable at
and go out there and perform." So to me,
that's what stands out about Proday.
>> Fellas, the combine is done. The pro
days are done and we are just under two
weeks away from the NFL draft. We will
officially be on the clock for the 2026
NFL draft out in Pittsburgh. We have the
number seven pick and we going to have
boots to the ground. myself alongside
Santana Moss and Brian Mitchell will be
there live for round one waiting to see
what Washington will do with the seventh
overall pick. Now let's take a look at
the full list of picks that we have here
in Washington. The Commanders currently
do not have a second or fourth fellas.
Remember we traded those to get left
tackle Laramie Tonsel last March and we
added a sixround pick when we sent
running back Brian Robertson Jr. to San
Fran. Fellas, a lot of opportunities to
win this draft. But let's get right into
it. It's time for securing the W
presented by Hercules Fence. Security in
every job, fellas. We continue to move
closer to the draft. Like I said, just
two weeks away. Logan, I'm going to
start with you because during this
process of the pro days, guys really get
a chance to show what they can do. We
even hosted an IP proday, an
international players pathway proday in
conjunction with the H.B.CU combine. Why
is this part of the draft process so
important?
>> I think it's so important because guys,
teams are finalizing their boards,
right? They're looking kind of for
anybody in that kind of 150 to 250 to
kind of deserve to be on the board,
right? I think in with the pathway
program uh pro that they did here like
you are Bernard, the guy from Nigeria,
he's 6'5, he's two he's 310 lbs, 1010
broad jump, he's 5% body fat, he's got
36 inch arms. Like all of a sudden I
look down the board, I'm like, who is
that mutant freak? Let's put him on our
list, man. Because we can develop that
guy. If you get a guy in the seventh
round that can develop into a starter
based on traits, that's what you're
looking for. So all these pro days
across the country are giving guys
opportunities to kind of say, "Hey man,
I am this athlete. I wasn't utilized
like this at the school." So that's
where the value is for, man. Everyone
wants to show the quarterbacks all that
stuff. It's for the guys that were role
players in college that have better
measurables than people think and have
those measurables that fit the NFL game.
>> And Fred, I think you're somebody great
to talk about this because you decided
not to do a combine. You were a top
prospect, but you said, "I want to do my
workouts at my pro day."
>> I was I mean, he was a second round
pick.
>> No, no, no. I was SUPPOSED TO PUT IT
SUPPOSED TO BE A FIRST ROUND PICK. LET'S
GET IT ALL RIGHT. BUT HIS MOUTH GOT IN
THE WAY.
>> But it's one of them things.
>> It's one of them things where yeah,
you're comfortable at home. You want to
put on a showcase at home. All right. I
get to be around my guys, but it it
ain't just for me. I I want you to come
here and see the rest of my teammates
that's going to try to go to the league,
too. And that's why I love what Mendoza
did in Indiana. He knew I'm going to do
my personal workout. He already said, "I
want to showcase Omari Cooper. I want to
showcase SRA. I want to showcase
everybody else." So having that platform
to to showcase yourself at home where
you comfortable at, I think sometimes
gives your best performance.
>> Tanny, was that the same for you and
your pro day?
>> Yeah, I mean mine surprisingly I didn't
know I was that big of a deal uh leading
into my proday until I told them that I
wasn't going to work out, you know what
I mean? Um at the combine and most of
the scouts and the guys there, I don't
know if they were trying to pull my leg,
but they was like, "Well, we not showing
up if you don't do anything." Wow. Fast
forward, all 30ome teams came and it was
so many other guys that got a chance to
kind of benefit from that. So, you know,
I learned then, you know, real fast that
I had a lot of weight. I was pulling a
lot of weight. But it was one of those
things, man, when I went out there, I I
wasn't trying to just, you know, like,
you know, I guess you can say belittle
anybody cuz they were at the combine. I
just felt like we had set a tone for
oursel as what we put on tape
>> from my school alone, my, you know,
University of Miami that they know we
can play football. Let me do it
comfortably. Let me do it where these
people not picking and pulling on me at
at home where I can go out there and
really struck my stuff.
>> And how different is it now, man? Like
there's over 100 NFL 100 NFL personnel
at the Miami Proday this year because
like that's the expectation for these
players. They've they own this process
now and the proday is a great platform
to get that done because you are more
comfortable there. Like you're going to
sleep in your own bed, run on your own
grass. Like it's important. It's it's
the most important.
>> You've been there for four years.
>> It's the most important job interview
you're ever going to do. Like be
comfortable. And I gota imagine it
affects those later round guys as well,
Logan, because I'm thinking of going to
go watch Tana. Well, Mary, there's a guy
on that roster that we didn't even know
to look at, but he's getting off his
loves while we watch.
>> We had a guy, Andre King, he was a
receiver, played played with us, came
in, he was an older guy. He came in from
minor league baseball. Um, he was, I
believe, 26 or 27 when we all said we
was rookies and we was like, 20 what?
And I tell you not, he put up good film,
but that pro day killed
>> and he ended up getting drafted to the
uh Cleveland Browns. And and to me, I
think the pro day is what sealed it for
him. Although our head coach from from
our university end up being the head
coach there, but everybody else was
bought in, you know, from just what he
did that pro day.
>> Yeah. And I think the other one too,
like a more precient example at Miami is
Keant Scott. Everyone's like, how fast
is he going to be? Guys runs a 4-3 at
home. Like that's that's the value. He
is now probably a second round draft
pick from going going from a day three
prospect just because of what he did to
proday.
>> Logan, great to have you back in the
building. Man, you know, we're so happy
to have you back. We gave you your own
little segment. It is time for Logan's
top five presented by UA Local 5
Plumbers protecting the health of the
nation's capital since 1890. Now Logan,
after months of evaluating, you dropped
this list of five prospects from this
draft class that you think will be
guaranteed ballers. That's a direct
quote from Logan Paulson. Now, how did
you come up with this five, sir?
>> Yeah, I mean these guys are all like
easy, right? Jeremiah Love, Sunny
Styles, those are blue chip players in
this draft class. Jeremy Bernard maybe
the most polished receiver you're going
to get in the second round. Mai Lemon is
an absolute dog competitor. And Tanner
Kier, man, 67, 34 in arms, plays above
the rim. Love that in the red zone.
>> Love that. Now, if you want to hear more
from Logan breaking down all of these
prospects, you can listen to Drive to
the Draft podcast, wherever you get your
podcast. and you want more podcast
content, we have an exciting event on
deck for you. The Command Center podcast
crew will be live from Franklin Hall in
DC to celebrate the Commander New
Jersey. That's why we bringing you some
new jerseys. Fans can enjoy appearances
from Major Tutty, Command Force, and
some of your favorite Washington's
legends. There will also be exclusive
giveaways in a live Command Center
podcast. Now, if you are in the DMV, be
sure to join us at Franklin Hall or tune
in live right here on the Commander
YouTube page. You won't want to miss it.
And our guy Fred Smoot has the best seat
in the house right now. Let's check in
on our guy Fred. This is best seat in
the house presented by SeatGeek. The
most disruptive idea in ticketing a
ticket that works. Expect be expected.
Segeek.
Welcome to the new segment. Smoot says
everything. And I'm going to respond to
the fans and anything that y'all say on
YouTube or any other social media splash
we got. Starting with Overthinker
1710.
He says, "Man, sir Delaney is a
difference maker. We have a superior
quarterback who will make everyone on
offense better. So, we need to soar up
the defense." Now, how I feel about this
is you can't compare a quarterback to a
quarterback. That ain't the way it goes.
All right. The value just not there. Do
I like Manor Delaney? Yes, I do. But I
like McCoy from Tennessee just a tad bit
more. I think he's the dog. Both of them
are dogs. YOU CAN'T GO WRONG WITH either
one. But I'm sorry, overthinker. You
overthought it. All right, go to the
next one. All right, coming from James
Benjamin. I like the name. You got to go
with Styles if he's there at seven. If
not, then we got to go with love. All
right. I love me some Sunny Styles. I'm
just going to be honest with you. It
ain't too many animals like this in this
draft. If Sunny Styles is there, I'm
going to run it up there on the podium
and make sure they get it so we can get
Sunny Styles. And you're right. If Sunny
Styles is gone, then you can take a
Caleb DS. I'm not mad at you. You can't
go wrong. Just go to Ohio State, find
some athletes, and draft them. That's
the way it is. All right. Cloaky. All
right. Smoot is for the people. And you
are correct. And I always will be for
the people. What y'all say and what
y'all thinking, I spilled it out. I said
I'm always here for y'all. Commander
Land. We going to always going to stick
together. Back to you, BC. Shout out my
guy Smoot. Truly a man of the people.
Now, Command Center is your home for all
things 2026 NFL draft. The entire
Command Center crew, including Logan
Santana, Fred, London Fletcher, and
Shawn Springs, will be live for rounds 1
through three. And of course, Fred will
be amongst the people for round one at
the Commander Draft Party out at
Northwest Stadium. You won't want to
miss it. Be sure to tune in on the
Commander YouTube, Facebook, and X
starting at 7 p.m. on April 24th. And
speaking of Sean Springs, it's time to
welcome in a very, very special guest.
It's time for your campus moment
presented by FanDuel. Make every moment
more with FanDuel, an official partner
of the Washington Commander. Sean
Springs is in the building. Good to see
you, my brother. And I see you got those
Ohio State prospects behind you. I felt
like it was only right that we brought
the highest drafted guy out of Ohio
State here in Washington. What you go
number three?
>> You know, somewhere around there, man. I
went I went behind two other people.
That's all I know.
>> Thank for Travis Hunter. Thank
>> for Travis now.
>> DO YOU STILL FEEL LIKE YOU'RE THE
highest drafted defensive back in NFL
history or does Travis Hunter get that?
>> I don't know, man. It's all about For
me, it was never about the ranking. It
was It was all about just being honored
to go into the league, you know, like
just period. I didn't, you know, I'm I'm
humble with it. I'm not gonna say I was
number three. It was all It was just all
about just really, man, just at that
time, I was trying to be the best
defensive prospect, not just corner.
>> Look at your boy trying to act like he
humble.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know what? YOU KNOW
WHAT? THIS AIN'T THE TIME FOR you to be
HUMBLE RIGHT NOW. I'M GOING TO LET YOU
BRAG on your boys from Ohio State cuz
every time I look in a mock draft in the
top 10, I'm seeing four, five Ohio State
guys. I'M TALKING ABOUT SUNNY STYLES.
I'M TALKING ABOUT CARELL TATE, CALEB DS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT animal after animal
after animal. IF YOU HAD TO PICK ONE FOR
US TO TAKE AT SEVEN, IT IT IT JUST WHICH
ONE would it be?
>> If I had to pick one that would take at
seven, I mean, I don't think he's going
to be there, but that that Arll Reese,
man, I don't think people really
understand the type of animal. Well, I
guess we do because he's probably going
to go top three pick. Uh Arll is is is
is unbelievable. But for the best fit
for us, man, I like Sunny Styles or I
like Caleb DS cuz I think for our
defense, obviously we need some strength
down the middle of that field. And if
you add Caleb and Smooth, you know, when
you add a dude that can play at every
level of the field, Caleb can play deep,
he can play in the middle of the field,
he takes great angles, he can play at
the line of scrimmage, he can blitz, he
can do it all. So Caleb is a instant
impact at all three levels. But when you
just talk about for need and just pure
speed and you can plug him in the
middle, you know that Sunny's a freak,
man. His father Lorenzo was a teammate
of mine. He played middle linebacker,
all-American at Ohio State. And Sunny is
just one of those rare talents where you
can Fred and BC kind of put me in a
mindset of the Fred Warner type guy. One
of those guys who can he can play in
coverage because he plays safety and
he's long and athletic, but he can go
sideline to sideline. be physical enough
to take on blocks and everything.
>> Man, that is a lot of Buckeyes in that
top 10. All those prospects. I got to
imagine there's a little pride there for
you. I see you smiling, idiot.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, it it is pride, man, because
that's is just a testament of just what
Coach Day and those guys are doing up
there. You're talking about four guys
easily going in the top 10. And and we
could argue, right? We could argue that
Carell might be the best fit for us
because he just add, you know, a
receiver. Um, now you know the guys like
me and Smooth and London, we little
biased toward defensive guys because we
always want to see that that defense
bolstered, but if you plug Cardell into
this offense alongside Terry, who's
another Buckeye, you're talking about a
real productive receiver that got things
done this year at a high level.
>> The only thing Cardell Tate would not
like is he can't put on that 17 cuz Ohio
State Buckeye already got
>> uh true facts. facts about that. You
already got and he got some respect to
the OT.
>> Yeah, I gotta imagine the line up next
to Terry McLaren. I got to imagine he's
not going to mind switching his jersey
number. But Sean, we appreciate you so
much. The dynamic duo back together
again. Remember, you can catch them at
Northwest Stadium for the first round of
the draft. Sean, we appreciate your
time, brother.
>> All right. Thank you,
>> Blue.
>> My god. Shawn and Fred definitely some
bigname free agents back in their day.
And the Commanders welcomed in a
big-time free agent defensive back in
Amique Robertson. Now Robertson enters
his seventh season in the league after
stints with the Lions and the Las Vegas
Raiders. In 2025, Robertson put up 43
tackles and an interception for Detroit.
I had a chance to catch up with the
young corner about how he sees himself
fitting in to this defense. And you're
coming into a building where we have a
brand new defensive coordinator, Donte
Jones, but he is known to be somewhat of
a secondary whisperer, if you will. How
excited are you to see what Donte Jones
can unlock out of Amique Robertson?
>> Very very like I'm I'm I'm very excited,
man. You know, very cuz, you know, I
watched in previous years, you know,
from the sideline, you know, just
watching his guys out there, how they
flying around the ball, how they how
they getting those takeaways and wishing
that I, you know, man, I wish I could,
you know what I'm saying? So, it's like
now that I'm, you know, I'm in in that
style of defense, you know, I like I
said, I just can't wait to explode, man.
you know, and not only myself, I know
these younger guys, you know, they're
going to do the same thing as well.
>> Now, let's take a look at the winning
numbers brought to you by Maryland
Lottery. Please play responsibly. And
our guy 17 is chasing greatness, much
like our boy Mr. A to the N did back in
the day. Here is a list of the Commander
all-time receiving yards leader. You can
see Hall of Famer Art Monk at the top
spot. Washington legends Charlie Taylor
and Gary Clark. And of course, Mr. Eight
to the Nine with over 7,800 receiving
yards during his career here in
Washington. And then of course, Scary
Terry there at five. Now, Tana, before
this, you saw Terry and Jaden getting in
that work.
>> How important is that pre-season work,
right? That offseason work with your
peers, right? Because again, that was a
voluntary workout. How important are
those extra reps for being able to climb
up a list like this?
>> Yeah, I think uh one of the things about
you seeing Terry get along, you know, go
out there with his quarterback. He's not
worried about the list. He's worried
about making sure he can be sharp, you
know, come training camp, come when they
out here doing the stuff in the
springtime. Uh, but particularly just
for the season. You want to go out there
and make sure that we dotting all our
eyes, crossing all our tees. But it's
very important. I think that's where you
get the best stuff at in the offseason
when you're away from the camp and you
can go out there and just you guys can
just dive into what needs what's needed
from both parties. Hey, quarterback,
what you need from me? And then as the
receiver, you telling him, hey, when I'm
running these particular routes, I need
you to throw the ball this way and vice
versa. and you were part of some of the
more legendary offseason workouts, man.
There's a video that goes viral all the
time of you cutting it up with some of
the best to ever do it. Why was that
iron sharpening iron so important for
you to be there with your peers and put
that work?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think that's some of the
things that uh at that time and uh of
the day or of the our era,
>> those phones starting get to the point
to where now people recording things. We
was doing that before the phones. We was
doing that before people recorded it.
So, it wasn't new or nothing for us to
really go viral with because that's how
we was brought up in Miami. It was the
best against best. Whether you was
considered the best or not, we was
sharpening each other. We was making we
was giving each other that opportunity.
So, when we get a chance to get on this
platform, we can show the world what we
were. So, us being down there with a
little silly workout that we didn't
think would go nowhere. Now, it's just
something that every kid comes up to us
now and talk about, man, Andre Johnson,
Chad Johnson, Santana, you know, my son
was out there actually and a couple of
my homeboy. know, but that's just what
we were known for. When we get a chance
to go home, go home in the offseason,
whether you a University of Miami
Hurricane or not, we find ourselves
together down there just putting in the
work. I think the most important like
important impressive thing on that video
to me was your hat never moved. Now, one
time my boy cutting up grass
hair then, you know what I mean? I had
kept it right in there. Now, when you
look at Terry and Jaden getting that
work in that, a lot of times when you're
doing workouts, you're doing workouts
with all kind of different quarterbacks,
but Terry made sure to get those reps in
with Jaden. Why is that so important
with all the time both of them missed
together last year?
>> Yeah, I was just going to say that. You
see the time they lost last year. So, I
think they just getting ahead of the,
you know, ahead of the curve and saying,
"Hey, let's go out here and put these
reps in now."
>> Yeah, for sure, man. A lot of exciting
things this off season. Let's break down
a little bit more, fellas. What an off
season it's been. And it's crazy to
think it's that time of year again.
Santana's annual golf charity tournament
is here. But before we take our talents
to Tana's event,
>> Yeah. We got to run it back a little bit
to the last time, fellas. We were on the
green together. Let's check it out. This
is Mission Ready, powered by Big Bear
AI. Mission ready AI for a rapidly
evolving world.
>> Ah, you
mad, man.
>> Yes.
He hit it.
GET IN THERE.
THAT'S IT.
>> NOW, FELLAS, we have Tana's golf
tournament. You have a golf tournament
out in bay. So, our lovely producer
said, "You know what? Why don't we take
some practice shots before we get out
there and embarrass ourselves?" And
Logan, of course, you're the first one
to go, my brother. Set the tone.
>> We got to hit in the hole, right?
>> I think that's the goal.
Oh, let's go.
T, are you up next? Since
>> I'm trying to one up Fred cuz I know you
come up here and try to do something
smooth.
>> Do something special. I'm going hand.
>> You going to use one hand?
>> Oh, that's good.
>> Only one hand.
>> That's okay. Thank you. See what you
got. I'm the world's greatest gave you a
lot of tips now. So, he did. That boy
was Sugar Shane Mos. You should do it,
man.
>> I'm sure he has done. Uh-huh.
>> Whenever he start talking to himself,
it's going to be bad.
>> I'm talking.
>> Y'all looking good.
>> Y looking ready for Tanner's tournament.
Tana, man, tell them how they can still
contribute to the tournament if they
can.
>> So, it's for my foundation, 89 ways to
give. You can go to ww.89 ways to
give.org.
And I think it's one of those things,
man. I started this like in 2018. Uh the
co happened. We missed a couple years,
but it's been something that I've been
doing annually just to kind of raise
awareness and raise money for my
foundation and all the things I'm doing
in the community.
>> Always giving back to the community.
Like I said, Fred got one in May as
well. So, we going to make sure we pull
up. So, we don't see y'all at the
tournament. We will see y'all next week
on Command Center. I'm your host, Brian
Copa Jr. here with Logan Paul and Fred
Smooth. We stay to the nine Santana
Malls. Man, ain't no ball there.
Command Center was filmed at Big Bear AI
Command Center Studio. Big Bear AI
offers mission ready AI for a rapidly
evolving world.